Contact

irishgirlaz@live.com

www.linkedin.com/in/julie-flynn-405254123 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Intensive Care

Trauma Nursing

Vascular Access

Certifications

VA-BC

CNRN

Full Member

Full Member

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Julie Flynn

ICU SWAT RN at Banner University Medical Center Phoenix Mesa, Arizona

Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Continuous Renal Replacement Therapy, Working with Providers, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Patient Safety, member of Rapid Response Team, expert in peripheral vascular access with and without ultrasound, and strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Nursing from Arizona State University. Certifications of CCRN, CNRN, and VA-BC. Continued experience in acute care settings.

Clinical Ladder V since 2016. Daisy Award recipient January 2019.

Experience

Banner - University Medical Center 19 years 5 months

ICU SWAT RN

January 2007 - Present (13 years 7 months)

Trauma ICU RN

January 2002 - January 2007 (5 years 1 month)

Phoenix, Arizona Area

Nurse Extern

March 2001 - January 2002 (11 months)

Phoenix, Arizona

Education

Arizona State University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (1997 - 2001)